Twelve years. One love.
Something Like Summer is a romance, drama, music film directed by David Berry.
Something Like Summer traces the tumultuous relationship of Ben and Tim, secret high school
sweethearts who grow over the years into both adulthood enemies and complicated friends.
Benjamin Bentley, played by Grant Davis.
Tim Wyman, played by Davi Santos.
Jace Holden, played by Ben Baur.
Allison Cross, played by Ajiona Alexus.
Mrs. Bentley, played by Jana Lee Hamblin.
Mr. Bentley, played by Ron Boyd.
Something Like Summer is a 2017 drama musical film based upon the 2011 Young Adult novel
Something Like Summer by Jay Bell and the first entry in the Something Like...
The tone is emotional.